(Sheldon:)...and effect preceding cause.
(Sheldon:)So you are thinking of a universe.
It's not expanding from the center, no.
(Sheldon:)It is retreating
from a possibility space. Bam!
(Sheldon:)This is a space where we are all essentially
Alice standing in front of the Red Queen...
(Sheldon:)...and we're being offered a cracker
to quench our thirst.
(Sheldon:)Bam!
(Sheldon:)In another universe,
let's call that Universe Prime...
(Sheldon:)- ...there's another Sheldon...
- We should have let him go to bed.
(Leonard:)Bam.
(Leonard:)I can't believe we actually did it.
One thousand frigging Penny Blossoms.
(Penny:)I just want you guys to know
I am really grateful for your help...
(Penny:)...and for every dollar I make,
I'm gonna give you 20 cents.
(Howard:)That's your entire profit margin.
(Penny:)Oh. Then never mind.
(Leonard:)I'll print out the shipping label.